BHAVIK GILBERT

Software Engineer

- bhaviklob@hotmail.com
- → +447405805628
- Bhavik Gilbert
- Bhavik-Gilbert
- Portfolio Website

EDUCATION

Computer Science BSc (Hons)



King's College London

2021 - 2024

Awards

- · Associate of King's College London
- Professional Skills for a Globalised World

CS50 Online



Harvard University

2022

A-Levels

Mathematics, Computer Science Physics, Economics



Leyton VI Form College

2019 - 2021

SKILLS

- Python
- 🎍 lava
- Javascript (Node/ React/ Threejs)
- PHP

- \$\ \mathbf{s}\$ Scala
- SQL (MySQL/ Oracle)

INTERESTS

- Volleyball
- Badminton
- Travel

Awards

- Forage JPMC & Co Software **Engineering Virtual Experience**
- Duke of Edinburgh Bronze & Silver
- OFQUAL Open Awards Entry 3 Award in Employability and Professional Development (RQF)
- OpenLearn Introduction to software development & Technological innovation: a resource-based view

REFERENCES

• edwin.nganga@leyton.ac.uk

PROFILE

Driven by my passion for Tech, I've pursued a range of experiences to expand my knowledge around it. As a result, I've dabbled in several fields including: data analysis, game development, machine learning, web development and database systems. Proceeding forward, I plan to continue developing my knowledge as a software developer, adapting alongside new technologies and design structures, further improving my problem-solving and algorithmic.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Location Camp Support Assistant



Funtech

July 2022 - August 2022

- Managing and supporting tutors across 7 on-site locations to cultivate a safe and encouraging environment for learning
- Provided technical/IT/teaching support across courses, maintaining safeguarding standards, liaising with tutors and talking to clients and troubleshooting issues of all natures as they come up
- 3D Game Development(Unreal Engine), CyberSecurity(Kali Linux), Python(Basic/OOP/Pygame Development/AIML), Touch Typing, Roblox Development, Minecraft(Mods/Redstone) Development, Lego Robotics, Java(Basic)

Computer Science Mentor



LSC Leyton VI Form College

September 2021 - October 2022

- Advising students in all aspects of their coursework, ranging from usage in PHP, JavaScript, SQL, C# and Python
- Teaching students to design and document systems during the development process
- Technologies focusing on web development, database systems, unity 3D game development, python 2D game development and AI development

Computer Science Teacher



Funtech

July 2021 - August 2021

- Taught classes of up to 6 ranging from 6 16 years in age
- Lego Robotics, 3D Game Development (Unreal Engine), CyberSecurity (Kali Linux), Python(OOP/Tensorflow AIML)

PROJECTS

Deafblind Social Media Application

JPMorgan Code For Good Hackathon, NGO: DeafBlind UK

Group Project - 5 Contributors

- Python/SQL Web Application & MySQL Database(Flask/ColorBlind/PIL/CV2/DeepFace)
- Social Media website where users can post text, images, blogs and events specially built for deafblind people
- Facial Recognition Login, Integrated Google Sign-in, Image Colour Daltonization, Alt Text, Text to Speech, Unlimited Image Magnification, Simple & Accessible UI/UX Design

Property Portfolio Viewer Application

Group Project - 4 Contributors

- Java GUI Application(JavaFx, WebView)
- Application to allow users to view Airbnb properties, get information about them and their location such as crime rate, transport links and average price point.

Photography Booking & Management System

Solo Project - 1 Contributor

- PHP/Javascript/SQL Web Application Booking System & SQL Database
- Booking system to allow clients to hire photographers alongside enabling admins to effectively manage sales and view progress

Visit my portfolio website for more information